So now let's talk about the integration of Amazon bedrock and a service called CloudWatch.
So CloudWatch is a way for you to do cloud monitoring.
So CloudWatch has many services but you can have metrics,
you can have alarms, you can have logs and so on in CloudWatch and you them all.
And many services and areas have integration with CloudWatch.
So for Amazon bedrock, what you can do is you can do model invocation logging.
And that's something that can come up at the exam.
So the idea is that you want to send all the invocations,
so all the inputs and the outputs of model invocations into either CloudWatch logs or Amazon history.
And this can include the text, the images as well as the embeddings.
And this is very helpful because you get a history of everything that happened within bedrock.
On top of it, you can analyze the data further and build alerting on top of it.
Thanks to CloudWatch logs inside, which is a service which allows you to analyze the logs in real time from CloudWatch logs.
So the idea here is that we get full tracing and monitoring of bedrock thanks to CloudWatch logs.
The other one is CloudWatch metrics.
So the idea is that Amazon bedrock is going to publish a lot of different metrics to CloudWatch.
And then you can appear in CloudWatch metrics.
And some of them may be for general usage of bedrock, but some of them may also be related to guardrails.
So there's one called content filter count, which helps you understand if some content was filtered from a guardrail.
And so we can do with it is that once you have these kind of metrics in CloudWatch metrics,
you can build CloudWatch alarms on top of them to get alerted, for example,
when something is caught by a guardrail or when Amazon bedrock is exceeding a specific threshold for a specific metric.
So model invocation logging and CloudWatch metrics are very important in Amazon bedrock and there are topics that can appear in the exam.
So I hope you liked it and I will see you in the next lecture.